goodexperience.com 2003-12-06

# goodexperience.com - customer experience, user experience

**Good Experience Privacy Policy**

We will not sell your information to third parties. Details below. 

Privacy Statement 

This policy applies to all information obtained through this website as well the Good Experience newsletter. The term "we" includes Mark Hurst, the owner of Good Experience and goodexperience.com, and employees (if any) of goodexperience.com and the Good Experience newsletter. 

The privacy of your nonpublic information is important to us. This includes, but is not limited to, your name, email address and your subscription to our newsletter, if applicable. We use safeguards to protect your privacy and confidentiality. This disclosure discusses information we collect and the manner in which it is used. 

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update or modify our privacy policy by contacting, individually, those persons whose information we have gathered and offering the individual the opportunity to either "opt-in" or "opt out" of remaining on our lists. Should the individual not specifically "opt-in" to remain on the list, they will have been deemed to have "opted-out" and their information shall be permanently removed within twenty-four (24) hours from our records. 

Information Collection 

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Website and read the information contained on the Web pages, we may gather certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We may automatically gather the Internet domain, IP address from which you access our Website, and the date and time you access our website and the pages you visit. This is done to assist us in determining the value and quality of our webpages and website and to monitor our traffic for purposes of software and hardware integrity and maintenance. 

We may collect nonpublic personal information from you when you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information to us through our website. This information may include such information as name, address (email or postal service), telephone, financial information (personal or business), business information (including but not limited to corporate structure, employees names and contact information, corporate financial information), business addresses (email or postal service), business practices and preferences and any other information which we may gather from you in an effort to provide the best individualized service possible (which includes any information you may provide in response to any question we may ask you). If you subscribe to the Good Experience newsletter, we maintain your email address. 

It has always been, and shall remain, the belief that this information is for internal use only and will never, under any circumstance (excluding requirements under the law) be distributed, assigned, sold or transferred to third parties. 

Employees 

We may view information that you provide us in order to perform their jobs and service you. We restrict access to nonpublic information to those employees (if any) who need to know that information in order to provide services to you. 

Sharing Information 

We do not share information, public or nonpublic, with third parties unless required to under law. WHEN YOU PROVIDE INFORMATION TO goodexperience.com OR SUBSCRIBE TO THE NEWSLETTER YOU CAN REST ASSURED THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL NEVER BE SHARED WITH A THIRD PARTY WITHOUT YOUR EXPRESS CONSENT. 

Sale of Information 

Under no circumstances will goodexperience.com, Mark Hurst or any of their affiliates sell, assign, trade or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information, including, but not limited to, your name and email address. It has always been, and will always be, the policy of goodexperience.com and Mark Hurst that your privacy is very important. 

Questions If you have questions about our privacy policy, you may contact Mark Hurst at mark @(SPAMBLOCK) goodexperience.com. 

Good Experience and goodexperience.com are owned by and exclusive trademarks of Mark Hurst. 

Get e-mail updates of goodexperience.com: e-mail [update@goodexperience.com](mailto:update@goodexperience.com)

Copyright 1999-2003, Good Experience, Inc.
